wyscout.com 2014-10-20

# Privacy Policy | Wyscout

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Information regarding the processing of personal data pursuant to article 13 D. Decree 30 June 2003, n. 196 (the protection of personal data law – the “ **Code** “).  
Before accessing and using Wyscout it is important to carefully read the Information about how Wyscout processes your personal data. This information is provided to help all users consciously decide whether to begin to use or continue using Wyscout and to describe how Wyscout uses the data and personal information of its users.  
Upon registration and account creation, you agree to the Terms of Service of Wyscout (http://wyscout.com), and confirm that you have read the Information regarding how Wyscout processes personal data, as well as give Wyscout consent to process your personal data as described below, which is always in compliance with Italian legislation.  
This Information relates solely to the Wyscout’s website http://wyscout.com (hereinafter the “ **Platform** ”) and is not otherwise applicable.  
For the purposes of this Information on the processing of personal data, “Wyscout” refers to both the Platform and the company Wyscout Spa, with legal office in Corso Garibaldi 32/8, 16043 Chiavari (GE), fiscal code and VAT number 01499880993.

**Data controller**

The data controller is **Wyscout Spa** , with legal office in Corso Garibaldi 32/8, 16043 Chiavari (GE).

**Personal information collected and processing**

When accessing for the first time the Platform, you are required to create your own account by disclosing your personal information, among which, as a mere example: name, surname, e-mail address, telephone number and the company you are affiliated with. Once the registration form has been filled out, by clicking on [ **I have read and accept Privacy Policy** ] you give your consent to the processing, by Wyscout, of your personal data and information collected during the registration and account creation process. It is important that you carefully read the Information about how Wyscout processes your personal data before clicking on  **I have read and accept Terms and Conditions**.  
The disclosure of your personal information is necessary for the above mentioned purposes, and if you fail to give such consent you will not be able to use Wyscout and the services provided on the Platform.  
Wyscout will be able, with your consent, process your personal data, in particular your e-mail address, to send you newsletters and commercial offers. The disclosure of your personal data for this particular purpose is not necessary to allow you to use Wyscout’s services, however, if you do not give your consent, you will not receive information that might be of interest for you. You can give your consent for the processing of your personal data for the above mentioned purpose when creating your account by choosing the desired option (“Yes” or “No”).  
When choosing, please remember that you will be anytime able to revoke your consent in relation to commercial communication from Wyscout by writing to [•]@wyscout.com or by following the procedure described in the text of the communications received.  
Please remember that, notwithstanding what you have chosen, Wyscout will send you anyway a message anytime there is a substantial modification of the Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use.

**Personal information of third parties**

What you share through your account on Wyscout may contain also personal information of third parties.  
Wyscout does not collect and process personal information different from the ones collected directly from its users upon registration and account creation, however, since what you share through your account is accessible by other Wyscout’s users that can access the reserved area on the Platform, those other users can collect and use the contents that you share, which may include third parties’ personal information.  
Wyscout is not responsible for any unlawful processing of any third parties’ personal information nor for any processing of such data by any other user.

**Personal information concerning payments**

Through the Platform you can purchase, in compliance with the applicable Italian legislation and the Terms of Use of Wyscout [[ **http://wyscout.com/terms-and-conditions**](http://wyscout.com/terms-and-conditions)], packages of the services made available by Wyscout; the payment of the such packages’ price can be made by wire transfer or credit card.  
Wyscout will collect and process data for billing and transaction purposes to process the payments made by you in relation to the purchase of the packages made available by Wyscout on the Platform.  
The disclosure of your personal information is necessary for the above mentioned purpose, and if you fail to do so you will not be able to use Wyscout and purchase the packages of services made available by Wyscout on the Platform.

**Data Storage**

Your personal data are stored and processed by means of computerized procedures on secure servers and databases localized in the European Union.  
For safety reasons, a backup of users’ data will be made periodically.  
Wyscout undertakes to take all measures necessary for the security of the personal information collected and guarantees that the processing of personal information is carried out in strict compliance with applicable Italian legislation.  
Please remember that your account is protected by the password you have been given upon registration and account creation on the Platform. You are the sole responsible for the security of your password and must to be careful and keep the password secret and strictly private.

**Data communication and transmission**

Your personal data, collected and processed by Wyscout, will be made accessible exclusively to subjects that will be appointed for the processing of such data.  
Your personal data could be disclosed to the following categories.  
Companies controlled by, controlling or under common control with Wyscout or its affiliates.  
Wyscout may disclose your personal information to other companies controlled by, controlling or under common control with Wyscout or its affiliates, or service providers specifically identified and authorized by Wyscout or other subjects with which Wyscout has entered into cooperation agreements in relation to the Platform or the provision of services covered by the Platform.  
The above mentioned categories of subjects will process personal data only within the limits of what will be required to provide, on behalf of Wyscout, the services as well as complementary and indispensable services necessary to use the Platform and in any case, always in accordance with the requirements described in this Privacy Policy and in full compliance with Italian legislation.  
Wyscout will not disclose personal information collected from you, except to the subjects indicated above.

**Your rights**

You are entitled to the rights provided for by Article 7 of the Code, namely: to obtain a confirmation of the existence or otherwise of his/her own personal data from the Data Controller, which must be provided in an intelligible form which identifies the identity of the holder and the persons to whom the data may be communicated; to obtain updates, rectification and integration of his/her personal data, as well as its deletion, transformation into anonymous form, or the blocking of communication of his/her personal data which is in  violation of the law.  
You can exercise your rights as described above at any time by writing to [info@wyscout.com](mailto:info@wyscout.com).  
At the same e-mail address you can make any request of clarification in regard to the processing of personal data or the Wyscout Privacy Policy, as well as any requests for the deletion of personal data.

**Changes and updates on the processing of personal data**

The abovementioned information on the processing of personal data can be modified and / or updated any time.  
Wyscout will promptly inform you when significant changes are made in the processing of personal data by e-mail. You are still required to periodically verify the Privacy Policy, which is always available at the web address [http://www .wyscout.com/](http://www%20.wyscout.com/).
